http://www.mill-max.com/about/privacy

Skip to main content
Privacy Policy
Mill-Max Mfg. Corp. takes your privacy seriously. We treat your personal information responsibly and are committed to protecting your privacy and the confidentiality of the information you share with us. This Privacy Policy provides an overview of how we collect, use, and secure your personal information.What Information is Collected and How We Use ItCOLLECTION AND USEMill-Max primarily markets and sells our products and services to other businesses (B2B) and not directly to consumers. We collect personal and non-personal information about you only to the extent necessary to provide requested services and only if you voluntarily provide it to us.ActivityInformation CollectedCreate an Account, Place a Sample OrderName, email address, mailing address, phone number, companyNewsletter Sign-UpName, email address; Optional: countrySubmit a Job ApplicationName, email address, phone number; Optional: mailing address, country, resume/attachmentSubmit an Inquiry, Contact UsName, email address, phone number; Optional: mailing address, country, attachment SHARING AND DISCLOSUREMill-Max does not buy, sell, rent, or otherwise disclose personal information in exchange for financial considerations.Mill-Max may engage third parties to provide the requested service(s) and support our legitimate business purposes, including:Fulfilling an orderResponding to inquiries through communication with authorized distribution partners in your geographical areaMaintaining our website and supporting our newsletter through authorized processorsHow Do We Store and Safeguard Your InformationAll personal information collected by Mill-Max is stored on secure servers in the United States and we employ administrative, technical, and physical security measures, including data encryption in transit and at rest. The information is retained only as long as is necessary to comply with our business and legal obligations.Cookies and Tracking TechnologyThe Mill-Max website uses three types of cookies and web tracking technology to support our site, allow us to improve our services, and be consistent with visitor’s interests.Strictly Necessary Cookies: these cookies are essential to your ability to browse the site and use its features.Performance Cookies: these cookies collect data associated with how you use our site, like which pages you visited and what links you clicked on.Marketing Cookies: these cookies track your online activity to help advertisers deliver more relevant ads to you while browsing other sites.CookiesCookie TypeDescriptionGoogle Tag ManagerStrictly NecessaryAllows Mill-Max to manage and deploy the other cookies on our websiteGoogle Analytics, SharpspringPerformanceStores a unique ID that is used to generate statistical data on how you use our website*Adroll Roundtrip, Google Adword, Twitter Advertising, Bing Ads, Facebook AdsMarketingStores a unique ID that is used to present relevant advertisements, measure the effectiveness of the advertisements, and/or gather statistics on website visits and page views* * Mill-Max does not store the unique ID’s generated by any of the Performance or Marketing cookies with other personal information that may be gathered from your direct interactions with our website.These external resources provide detailed information about types of cookies, how they are used, and how you can manage your cookie preferences:All About CookiesFirefoxInternet ExplorerChromeYour Data RightsMill-Max will make all reasonable efforts to comply with any requests received. Any individual that voluntary signs up to receive the Mill-Max newsletter may opt-out at any time by:Clicking on the Unsubscribe link available in the footer of each newsletterContact us directly through the Contact Us formContact us directly using the information provided belowVisitors and Customers in the European UnionIf you are an individual, citizen, or resident within the European Economic Area, you may have the following rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR):Right to access of the personal information Mill-Max maintains about youRight to rectification of your personal informationIn certain circumstances: right to request erasure, right to the restriction and/or objection of processingRight to data portabilityVisitors and Customers in CaliforniaIf you are a California resident, you may have the following rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA):Right to know the personal information Mill-Max maintains about youRight to opt-out of the sale of your personal information (which is not a processing activity Mill-Max engages in)Right to non-discriminationIn certain circumstances: right to request deletionContact InformationIf you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy or practices, or wish to exercise your rights as described above, please contact us via:Email:Through the Contact Us pagePhone:516-922-6000 Thank you for visiting Mill-Max.com.
About
About Mill-Max
COVID-19 Operational Impact
Employment
Newsletter Signup
Quality Assurance
Environmental Compliance
×
